<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on Quantitative Analysis of the British Parliament</title><link>https://github.com/DanielHolmelund/the-political-debate-in-britain-illuminated-through-quantitative-methods/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on Quantitative Analysis of the British Parliament</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://github.com/DanielHolmelund/the-political-debate-in-britain-illuminated-through-quantitative-methods/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data description</title><link>https://github.com/DanielHolmelund/the-political-debate-in-britain-illuminated-through-quantitative-methods/data-description/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/DanielHolmelund/the-political-debate-in-britain-illuminated-through-quantitative-methods/data-description/</guid><description>What is the data - and where does is come from? The transcripts from the British parliament is freely avaliable and published by the britsh government to the public. This project however made use a precollected dataset spanning a period approximately six years. From 05-01-2015 to 01-03-2021. This dataset was made avaliable in relation to a multilingial analysis of different parliamentary debates, with the main focus being the debate around COVID.</description></item><item><title>Discussion</title><link>https://github.com/DanielHolmelund/the-political-debate-in-britain-illuminated-through-quantitative-methods/discussion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/DanielHolmelund/the-political-debate-in-britain-illuminated-through-quantitative-methods/discussion/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Network analysis</title><link>https://github.com/DanielHolmelund/the-political-debate-in-britain-illuminated-through-quantitative-methods/network-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/DanielHolmelund/the-political-debate-in-britain-illuminated-through-quantitative-methods/network-analysis/</guid><description>Network Analysis of the British Parliament Speeches The following section will attempt to analyse the political activity within the British Parliament by leveraging the results of the text analysis of the speeches in the previous section combined with methods from the network science field.
The first step in the analysis is to construct a network using the speech transcripts and associated metadata, which can be found in the data section. One possible approach for construction of the network is to create a bipartite network with one partition being the members of the Parliament and the other partition being political topics discovered in the text analysis section.</description></item><item><title>Text analysis</title><link>https://github.com/DanielHolmelund/the-political-debate-in-britain-illuminated-through-quantitative-methods/text-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/DanielHolmelund/the-political-debate-in-britain-illuminated-through-quantitative-methods/text-analysis/</guid><description>Analysing Speeches From Each Party
The following section will attempt to analyse the speeches conducted by each political party by finding descriptive and informative words from the transcripts. Initially, all the transcripts in the corpus were grouped by political party resulting in 47 documents corresponding to each party. The approach of the analysis stems from a simple idea, counting. More specifically, to discover descriptive words associated with the 47 documents, the frequency of occurence for each term will be computed, also refered to as term-frequency.</description></item></channel></rss>